<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://theme697-fitness-store.myshopify.com/blogs/news.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://theme697-fitness-store.myshopify.com/blogs/news"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://theme697-fitness-store.myshopify.com/blogs/news/tagged/t-shirts.atom"/>
  <title>Fitrue - News</title>
  <updated>2019-05-28T10:49:00-04:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Fitrue</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://theme697-fitness-store.myshopify.com/blogs/news/to-be-in-a-good-shape-is-very-important-nowadays</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T10:49:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T10:50:22-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://theme697-fitness-store.myshopify.com/blogs/news/to-be-in-a-good-shape-is-very-important-nowadays"/>
    <title>To be in a good shape is very important nowadays.</title>
    <author>
      <name>Odin Om</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Most of us spend endless hours sitting by the computer and it gives negative results very fast. We think that fitness is a pleasant and useful activity. It helps to be more successful and disciplined. We are trying to introduce positive results of our explorations.<br><strong>Our store has a largest assortment among the others that is</strong> why our products have a great number of faithful customers all over the country.We are proud to present our outstanding choice of sport &amp; fitness equipment. Our store has a largest assortment among the others that is why our products have a great number of faithful customers all over the country. <br>Keep saving your money with our store. There is no doubt that our products are the real bestsellers; our clients’ testimonials can prove that. Our products are the combination of attractive shapes and good content.</p>
<p><strong>We understand:</strong></p>
<ol>
<li>Home Gym Equipment</li>
<li>Yoga</li>
<li>Training equipment</li>
<li>Limit collections </li>
<li>Accessories</li>
</ol>
<h2>Keep saving your money with our store</h2>
<p>It helps to be more successful and disciplined.You must address our outstanding online 24/7 support system where you can find all answers on your questions. Also our company often provides different promos and you can get a good discount. The premium quality and fair price – these are the main advantages of our goods. <br>There is no doubt that our products are the real bestsellers; our clients’ testimonials can prove that.To be in a good shape is very important nowadays because our way of life isn’t so healthy and active. Most of us spend endless hours sitting by the computer and it gives negative results very fast. </p>
<p><iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/zXfSJyOuaZg" allowfullscreen="" height="720" width="1280"></iframe></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://theme697-fitness-store.myshopify.com/blogs/news/our-store-has-a-largest-assortment-among-the-others-that</id>
    <published>2019-05-28T10:47:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-28T10:50:32-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://theme697-fitness-store.myshopify.com/blogs/news/our-store-has-a-largest-assortment-among-the-others-that"/>
    <title>Our store has a largest assortment among the others that.</title>
    <author>
      <name>Odin Om</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>To be in a good shape is very important nowadays because our way of life isn’t so healthy and active.We are proud to present our outstanding choice of sport &amp; fitness equipment. Our store has a largest assortment among the others that is why our products have a great number of faithful customers all over the country.</p>
<p><a href="-">The premium quality </a>and fair price – these are the main advantages of our goods. You must address our outstanding online 24/7 support system where you can find all answers on your questions. Keep saving your money with our store.       <iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/zXfSJyOuaZg" allowfullscreen="" height="720" width="1280"></iframe></p>
<p>Also our company often provides different promos and you can get a good discount.</p>
<ul>
<li>Home Gym Equipment</li>
<li>Yoga</li>
<li>Training equipment</li>
<li>Limit collections </li>
<li>Accessories</li>
</ul>
<p>We think that fitness is a pleasant and useful activity.We are proud to present our outstanding choice of sport &amp; fitness equipment. Our store has a largest assortment among the others that is why our products have a great number of.The premium quality and fair price – these are the main advantages of our goods. Our products are the combination of attractive shapes and good content.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
